You will keep the stock of paid light on the radar. Yesterday the
listing of shares happened with a little moisture.
Here, Golmaal sex has
bought around 7.30 lakh shares
in the range of Rs 408 to 412, so that stock is on the radar
and today of course is 19th April, so land assets are bomb,
remember this will be seen getting listed today,
but we were discussing yesterday also that
this is 550 crore land
in Bangalore Mysore and it is estimated that the
company buys land worth 8400 crore, so land assets are bomb, it will be
listed today, ok
Ashish, I was actually going to give a comment,
after the ICC Lombard numbers, there was a
lot of build up in Haryana, we were
also watching it in the closing show yesterday, that means the stock is a
big relief, but the way the calls were
building up today, I feel
that tomorrow the buyers will have a little doubt,
wait a little after hearing the numbers in the result,
just take a call for profit numbers for a minute
and there is design and for that  On this basis, the
stock was pushed so much but the internals
are not that good and the positioning has become so
good, see, for this, now
what will be the trend in this, in this, the
green bar that they have made carefully, will
break first, when it comes below it,
when there is a stabilizer, I am thinking that it will
come from there because the numbers are not bad either,
but the numbers are not very good,
but the way the interest was built up yesterday at 1150 and
1200, yesterday there was two to three times increase,
in just half an hour so many buys were happening
there and so much high
cream on us and this will be a lesson
that you cannot take this method seriously,
we just have to go slowly, after that add,
you will get it sometime, okay and
actually see the front page performance of its front of
light etc.,
today we will watch out,
SBP Delight has acquired an American
asset, then you should closely
watch Asia Paint Light Charged Light,
how is it going, brother, the
physical light is very good, as per the satellite.  A
breakout has
come
which is very near buy, if it is bleached
then it is making a big mouth bandasta in it
which can reach the level of ₹2510,
so there is a buying trend, the
stopper to be maintained in these 11 delights is of 2380, there is
one
thing, PVR stock has moved ahead around the day's high,
sir, there is a
Salman Khan movie, that
could be a reason, nothing else, it seems a lot of
disrespect is being made, it seems to me that it
gives me display and nothing else,
like you give discussion of Reliance, I
think I am going to
watch it this evening, Baba Saheb, it is
releasing the day after tomorrow,
tomorrow morning at 7:15, I will buy it, I
told you that I will give a review of the movie,
okay
[laughs] I will
buy it as well
[music]